Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1946 -- 2013; 1983 -- 1994; UA002.002; 33.6 Linear Feet; 1 Web sites
  - Report Reviews, 1998 -- 2002; UA002.002.066.00008 (Box 66)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Workshops, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.066.00009 (Box 66)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Workshops, 1999 -- 2001; UA002.002.066.00010 (Box 66)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Workshops, 1996 -- 1998; UA002.002.066.00011 (Box 66)
  - Academic Council, 2003; UA002.002.066.00012 (Box 66)
  - Accreditation Team, 2006; UA002.002.066.00013 (Box 66)
  - ACGME, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.066.00014 (Box 66)
  - ADEA, 2003; UA002.002.066.00015 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Office, 1996 -- 1999; UA002.002.066.00016 (Box 66)
  - Affiliated Chiefs Meeting, 2003; UA002.002.066.00017 (Box 66)
  - Affiliations, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.002.066.00018 (Box 66)
  - Annual Report to the Dean, 2003; UA002.002.066.00019 (Box 66)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2004; UA002.002.066.00020 (Box 66)
  - APDIM, 1995; UA002.002.066.00021 (Box 66)
  - APUA, 2005; UA002.002.066.00022 (Box 66)
  - AT - Mini Institute, 2004; UA002.002.066.00023 (Box 66)
  - Awards, 2006; UA002.002.066.00024 (Box 66)
  - Blackberries, 2008; UA002.002.066.00025 (Box 66)
  - Board of Overseers, 2005; UA002.002.066.00026 (Box 66)
  - Broder Report, 1987; UA002.002.066.00027 (Box 66)
  - Brown University School of Medicine, 2006; UA002.002.066.00028 (Box 66)
  - Budget, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.066.00029 (Box 66)
  - Budget and University Priorities, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.066.00030 (Box 66)
  - CDC, 2003; UA002.002.066.00031 (Box 66)
  - Clerkship directors in internal medicine, 1991 -- 1996; UA002.002.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Clerkship directors in internal medicine, 1992; UA002.002.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - CDIM national meetings, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.002.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - CDIM national meetings, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.002.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Clerkship directors in internal medicine, 1992 -- 1995; UA002.002.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Clerkship directors in internall medicine, 1998; UA002.002.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - China, 2003; UA002.002.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Clerkship, 2001 -- 2003; UA002.002.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Commonwealth Fund task force on academic health centers, 2003; UA002.002.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Confidentiality agreement, 2000; UA002.002.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Consultants, 2004; UA002.002.067.00011 (Box 67)
  - Core, 2006; UA002.002.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Core collaborations, 1999 -- 2003; UA002.002.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Core medicine clerkships curriculum guide, 1998; UA002.002.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Council of deans, 2004; UA002.002.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - Crt final, 2005; UA002.002.067.00016 (Box 67)
  - Community service learning, 2003; UA002.002.067.00017 (Box 67)
  - Tufts Clinincal and Translational Science Institute revised CTSA application, 2007; UA002.002.067.00018 (Box 67)
  - CTSI, 2006; UA002.002.067.00019 (Box 67)
  - Curriculum committee, 2002 -- 2007; UA002.002.067.00020 (Box 67)
  - Curriculum development, 1996; UA002.002.067.00021 (Box 67)
  - Dartmouth Medical School, 2002; UA002.002.067.00022 (Box 67)
  - DCA, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.002.067.00023 (Box 67)
  - Dean Search, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Development, 2002; UA002.002.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - Development Presentation 10.6.05 - Mary Lee, 2005; UA002.002.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Drafts Final Proposal, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.002.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Early Wins, 2006; UA002.002.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - EBCAM, 2000 -- 2006; UA002.002.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - Evidence-Based Medicine (EBM), 2002 -- 2007; UA002.002.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Educational Retreat, 1997; UA002.002.068.00008 (Box 68)
  - Educational Strategic Planning Retreat 11.20.2006, UA002.002.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Einstein, 2004 -- 2011; UA002.002.068.00010 (Box 68)
  - EMD, 2002; UA002.002.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Educational Strategic Planning (ESP), 2004 -- 2007; UA002.002.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Ethics, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.002.068.00013 (Box 68)
  - Experimental College, 2005; UA002.002.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Faculty Development, 1 of 3, 1976 -- 1989; UA002.002.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Faculty Development, 2 of 3, 1999 -- 2004; UA002.002.068.00016 (Box 68)
  - Faculty Development, 3 of 3, 1983 -- 1986; UA002.002.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher Spaght, Inc., 2001; UA002.002.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - 81 - Fri Deans' Mtgs, 2002; UA002.002.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - AAMC Group on Educational Affairs (GEA), 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Geriatric Education, 2004; UA002.002.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - GIST Mtg, 10.9.03, 130-330pm, Coolidge Room, Ballou, 2003; UA002.002.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - Good Work Project, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.002.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - Graduate Programs, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.002.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Grants, 2002 -- 2004; UA002.002.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - Hewlett Foundation 1 of2, 2005; UA002.002.069.00002 (Box 69)
  - Hewlett Foundation 2 of2, 2005; UA002.002.069.00003 (Box 69)
  - Grants 1 of 2, 2003 -- 2005; UA002.002.069.00004 (Box 69)
  - Grants 2of 2, 1999 -- 2002; UA002.002.069.00005 (Box 69)
  - Gynecological exams on unconcious women, 2003; UA002.002.069.00006 (Box 69)
  - Harvard project zero, 2003; UA002.002.069.00007 (Box 69)
  - Geriatrics task force, 2003; UA002.002.069.00008 (Box 69)
  - Harvard Macy Institute: program for physician educators 1 of 4, 1995 -- 2006; UA002.002.069.00009 (Box 69)
  - Harvard Macy Institute: program for physician educators 2 of 4, 1994 -- 1996; UA002.002.069.00010 (Box 69)
  - Harvard Macy Institute: program for physician educators 3 of 4, 1996; UA002.002.069.00011 (Box 69)
  - Harvard Macy Institute: program for physician educators 4 of 4, 1996; UA002.002.069.00012 (Box 69)
  - Housestaff photos, 1988 -- 1994; UA002.002.069.00013 (Box 69)
  - HSDB, 2002; UA002.002.069.00014 (Box 69)
  - Huron Consulting Group, 2004; UA002.002.069.00015 (Box 69)
  - Health Insurance, 2004; UA002.002.069.00016 (Box 69)
  - HSDB steering committee, 2003; UA002.002.069.00017 (Box 69)
  - IEM, 2003; UA002.002.069.00018 (Box 69)
  - Information booklet, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.069.00019 (Box 69)
  - Information technology board, 2005; UA002.002.069.00020 (Box 69)
  - Innovation grants, 2005; UA002.002.069.00021 (Box 69)
  - Innovations grant, 2004; UA002.002.069.00022 (Box 69)
  - Institutional advancement design session, 2003; UA002.002.069.00023 (Box 69)
  - Information technology committee 1 of 2, 2004; UA002.002.069.00024 (Box 69)
  - Information technology committee 2 of 2, 2004; UA002.002.069.00025 (Box 69)
  - Information Technology Committee (ITC) [1 of 3], UA002.002.070.00001 (Box 70)
  - Information Technology Committee (ITC) [2 of 3], UA002.002.070.00002 (Box 70)
  - Information Technology Committee (ITC) [3 of 3], UA002.002.070.00003 (Box 70)
  - Interstation Exercise, 2002; UA002.002.070.00004 (Box 70)
  - ITEB, 2004; UA002.002.070.00005 (Box 70)
    Information Technology Executive Board
  - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 2002; UA002.002.070.00006 (Box 70)
  - 79 - Kathleen, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.070.00007 (Box 70)
  - Lahey, UA002.002.070.00008 (Box 70)
    Lahey Faculty Development Workshop
  - LCME, UA002.002.070.00009 (Box 70)
    Liaison Committee on Medical Education
  - Leadership Competency Model, UA002.002.070.00010 (Box 70)
  - Letters, UA002.002.070.00011 (Box 70)
  - Letters of Support, 2003; UA002.002.070.00012 (Box 70)
  - Macy Mentorship Program, 2006; UA002.002.070.00013 (Box 70)
  - Mail, 2003; UA002.002.070.00014 (Box 70)
  - Massachusetts Medical Society, 2002; UA002.002.070.00015 (Box 70)
  - Medbiquitous, 2006; UA002.002.070.00016 (Box 70)
  - Medical Simulation Working Group, 2005; UA002.002.070.00017 (Box 70)
  - Medcore, UA002.002.070.00018 (Box 70)
  - Medcore: Curriculum, UA002.002.070.00019 (Box 70)
  - Medcore: Meetings, UA002.002.070.00020 (Box 70)
  - Medcore, UA002.002.070.00021 (Box 70)
  - Med Foundations Working Group, UA002.002.070.00022 (Box 70)
  - Medinfo, 2004; UA002.002.071.00001 (Box 71)
  - MERC, 2005 -- 2006; UA002.002.071.00002 (Box 71)
  - Michael Whitcomb M.D. visit, 1999; UA002.002.071.00003 (Box 71)
  - MSOP, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.002.071.00004 (Box 71)
  - NBME, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.071.00005 (Box 71)
  - NCCAM, 2001 -- 2003; UA002.002.071.00006 (Box 71)
  - NEASC, 2003; UA002.002.071.00007 (Box 71)
  - AAMC Northeastern group on Educational affairs (NEGEA) 1 of 5, 2005; UA002.002.071.00008 (Box 71)
  - AAMC Northeastern group on Educational affairs (NEGEA) 2 of 5, 2004; UA002.002.071.00009 (Box 71)
  - AAMC Northeastern group on Educational affairs (NEGEA) 3 of 5, 2003; UA002.002.071.00010 (Box 71)
  - AAMC Northeastern group on Educational affairs (NEGEA) 4 of 5, 2002; UA002.002.071.00011 (Box 71)
  - AAMC Northeastern group on Educational affairs (NEGEA) 5 of 5, 1997; UA002.002.071.00012 (Box 71)
  - New England Medical Center (NEMC) 1 of 2, 2001 -- 2004; UA002.002.071.00013 (Box 71)
  - New England Medical Center (NEMC) 2 of 2, 1997 -- 2000; UA002.002.071.00014 (Box 71)
  - New Degrees, 1997 -- 2006; UA002.002.071.00015 (Box 71)
  - The New York Times, 2003; UA002.002.071.00016 (Box 71)
  - NHLBI, 2005; UA002.002.071.00017 (Box 71)
  - NHPH Boston Site Visit, 2005; UA002.002.071.00018 (Box 71)
  - Notes, 2004; UA002.002.071.00019 (Box 71)
  - Nuffic expert meeting 'A changing landscape', 2004; UA002.002.071.00020 (Box 71)
  - Nutter, 2003; UA002.002.071.00021 (Box 71)
  - Objectives Writing Workshop, 1996; UA002.002.071.00022 (Box 71)
  - OEA, 2005 -- 2006; UA002.002.071.00023 (Box 71)
  - OEA, 2005 -- 2008; UA002.002.071.00024 (Box 71)
  - Office of Institutional Research, UA002.002.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - Office of Medical Education, UA002.002.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - OGDP, UA002.002.072.00003 (Box 72)
    Office of Graduate Degrees and Special Programs
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [1 of 6], UA002.002.072.00004 (Box 72)
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [2 of 6], UA002.002.072.00005 (Box 72)
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [3 of 6], UA002.002.072.00006 (Box 72)
    MIT Files 1 of 2
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [4 of 6], UA002.002.072.00007 (Box 72)
    MIT Files 2 of 2
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [5 of 6], UA002.002.072.00008 (Box 72)
  - Open Course Ware (OCW) Initiative [6 of 6], UA002.002.072.00009 (Box 72)
  - Office of Dietary Supplements, UA002.002.072.00010 (Box 72)
  - Organizational Charts, UA002.002.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - OSCE, UA002.002.072.00012 (Box 72)
    Objective Structured Clinical Examination
  - PBL, UA002.002.072.00013 (Box 72)
    Problem-Based Learning
  - Pfizer, UA002.002.072.00014 (Box 72)
  - 56 - Pharm, UA002.002.072.00015 (Box 72)
    Board Stats
  - Photos, UA002.002.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - Physical Diagnosis, UA002.002.072.00017 (Box 72)
  - Presentations, UA002.002.072.00018 (Box 72)
  - Program Evaluation Certificate, UA002.002.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - Program for Leaders in Healthcare Education, 2005; UA002.002.072.00020 (Box 72)
  - 76 - Projects, UA002.002.073.00001 (Box 73)
  - Program Suggestions, UA002.002.073.00002 (Box 73)
  - PME, UA002.002.073.00003 (Box 73)
    Project Medical Education
  - Graduating Class Pictures, 1988 -- 2000; UA002.002.073.00004 (Box 73)
  - The Practice Group: Faculty/Student Advisor Program Handbook, 1997; UA002.002.073.00005 (Box 73)
  - Provost, 2002 -- 2006; UA002.002.073.00006 (Box 73)
  - Provost's Council, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.002.073.00007 (Box 73)
  - Provost Office, UA002.002.073.00008 (Box 73)
  - Provost Retreat, 2003 -- 2005; UA002.002.073.00009 (Box 73)
  - Provost's Staff Meeting, 2005; UA002.002.073.00010 (Box 73)
  - Provost's Working Group, 2002; UA002.002.073.00011 (Box 73)
  - Provost's Staff Meeting, 2004; UA002.002.073.00012 (Box 73)
  - Publications, UA002.002.073.00013 (Box 73)
    Medicine and Education
  - RAC, UA002.002.073.00014 (Box 73)
    Regional Advisory Committee
  - Reference, UA002.002.073.00015 (Box 73)
  - Reports [1 of 3], UA002.002.073.00016 (Box 73)
  - Reports [2 of 3], UA002.002.073.00017 (Box 73)
  - Reports [3 of 3], UA002.002.073.00018 (Box 73)
  - Reunions, 1983 -- 2008; UA002.002.073.00019 (Box 73)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Medical School, UA002.002.073.00020 (Box 73)
  - Senior Leaders, UA002.002.073.00021 (Box 73)
  - Siena University, UA002.002.073.00022 (Box 73)
  - Stanford Faculty Development Center, UA002.002.073.00023 (Box 73)
  - St. Elizabeth's Medical Center, UA002.002.074.00001 (Box 74)
  - Strategic Planning [1 of 4], UA002.002.074.00002 (Box 74)
  - Strategic Planning [2 of 4], UA002.002.074.00003 (Box 74)
  - Strategic Planning [3 of 4], UA002.002.074.00004 (Box 74)
  - Strategic Planning [4 of 4], UA002.002.074.00005 (Box 74)
  - Summer Institute, 2006; UA002.002.074.00006 (Box 74)
  - Survey, 2003 -- 2005; UA002.002.074.00007 (Box 74)
  - Trustee Academic Affairs Committee (TAAC) [3 of 3], UA002.002.074.00008 (Box 74)
  - Trustee Academic Affairs Committee (TAAC) [3 of 3], UA002.002.074.00009 (Box 74)
  - Trustee Academic Affairs Committee (TAAC) [3 of 3], UA002.002.074.00010 (Box 74)
  - FRAC TAAC, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.002.074.00011 (Box 74)
  - Tarnoff - Wise Project, UA002.002.074.00012 (Box 74)
  - Task Force on the Undergraduate Experience, UA002.002.074.00013 (Box 74)
  - TCSVM, UA002.002.074.00014 (Box 74)
    Tufts Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Team-Based Learning Collaborative, UA002.002.074.00015 (Box 74)
  - Technology, UA002.002.074.00016 (Box 74)
  - TISC Task Force Final Report, 1997; UA002.002.074.00017 (Box 74)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute (TMCI) [1 of 2], UA002.002.074.00018 (Box 74)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute (TMCI) [2 of 2], UA002.002.074.00019 (Box 74)
  - Tufts-Cuba, UA002.002.074.00020 (Box 74)
  - The Tufts Daily, UA002.002.074.00021 (Box 74)
  - Tufts IMS, 2004; UA002.002.074.00022 (Box 74)
    Identity Management
  - Tufts Nutrition, UA002.002.074.00023 (Box 74)
  - Tufts University Medical Alumni Association, UA002.002.074.00024 (Box 74)
  - TUSK Grants [1 of 2], UA002.002.074.00025 (Box 74)
    Tufts University Sciences Knowledgebase
  - TUSK Grants (2 of 2), 1995 -- 1999; UA002.002.075.00001 (Box 75)
  - TUSK Notes, 2004 -- 2006; UA002.002.075.00002 (Box 75)
  - TUSK Papers, 2007; UA002.002.075.00003 (Box 75)
  - TUSK Strategic Planning, 2004; UA002.002.075.00004 (Box 75)
  - Admissions Committee, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.075.00005 (Box 75)
  - Accredidation, 2005; UA002.002.075.00006 (Box 75)
  - Affiliated Chief of Medicine, 2003; UA002.002.075.00007 (Box 75)
  - Annual Reports, 2006; UA002.002.075.00008 (Box 75)
  - Campus Visits, 2006; UA002.002.075.00009 (Box 75)
  - Class Schedule, 2007; UA002.002.075.00010 (Box 75)
  - Clerkship, 2004; UA002.002.075.00011 (Box 75)
  - Commencement, 2007; UA002.002.075.00012 (Box 75)
  - Core Clinical Task Force, 2003; UA002.002.075.00013 (Box 75)
  - Courses, 2004; UA002.002.075.00014 (Box 75)
  - Curriculum, 2000; UA002.002.075.00015 (Box 75)
  - Dashboard, 2004; UA002.002.075.00016 (Box 75)
  - Dean's Retreat, 1996 -- 2005; UA002.002.075.00017 (Box 75)
  - Evidence Based Medicine, 2005; UA002.002.075.00018 (Box 75)
  - Faculty Database, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.075.00019 (Box 75)
  - Fac Dev, 2004 -- 2005; UA002.002.075.00020 (Box 75)
  - Fac Dev Trainings (1 of 2), 1997 -- 1999; UA002.002.075.00021 (Box 75)
  - Fac Dev Trainings (2 of 2), 1996 -- 1997; UA002.002.075.00022 (Box 75)
  - Family Medicine, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.002.075.00023 (Box 75)
  - Final Fiscal Report, 2001; UA002.002.075.00024 (Box 75)
  - Geriatrics Retreat, 2005 -- 2006; UA002.002.075.00025 (Box 75)
  - Grants, 2007; UA002.002.075.00026 (Box 75)
  - Health Sciences Databases (1 of 3), 2000; UA002.002.075.00027 (Box 75)
  - Health Sciences Databases (2 of 3), 2000 -- 2001; UA002.002.075.00028 (Box 75)
  - Health Sciences Databases (3 of 3), 2000; UA002.002.075.00029 (Box 75)
  - "Light to the Hill" Report, 1998; UA002.002.075.00030 (Box 75)
  - Med Ed, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.002.075.00031 (Box 75)
  - Medicine Clerkship, UA002.002.076.00001 (Box 76)
  - Memo, UA002.002.076.00002 (Box 76)
  - NEMC, UA002.002.076.00003 (Box 76)
    New England Medical Center (later Tufts Medical Center)
  - Notes, UA002.002.076.00004 (Box 76)
  - Orientation, 2003 -- 2005; UA002.002.076.00005 (Box 76)
    Tufts University School of Medicine (TUSM)
  - Physiology Discussion Groups and Recitations, UA002.002.076.00006 (Box 76)
  - Presentations, UA002.002.076.00007 (Box 76)
  - Programs, UA002.002.076.00008 (Box 76)
  - Public Health, 2000; UA002.002.076.00009 (Box 76)
  - Reference, UA002.002.076.00010 (Box 76)
  - Report on Civic Engagement, UA002.002.076.00011 (Box 76)
  - Strategic Plan, 1999; UA002.002.076.00012 (Box 76)
  - Student Info, 2000 -- 2009; UA002.002.076.00013 (Box 76)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine 1893-1993, UA002.002.076.00014 (Box 76)
    Centennial Publication
  - Workshops, UA002.002.076.00015 (Box 76)
  - TUSM-UMASS, UA002.002.076.00016 (Box 76)
    Tufts University School of Medicine (TUSM), University of Masssachusetts partnership
  - UC Fellows, UA002.002.076.00017 (Box 76)
  - UCTFD, UA002.002.076.00018 (Box 76)
    University Committee on Teaching and Faculty Develoment
  - UIT, UA002.002.076.00019 (Box 76)
    University Information Technology
  - University Library Council (ULC) [1 of 2], UA002.002.076.00020 (Box 76)
  - University Library Council (ULC) [2 of 2], UA002.002.076.00021 (Box 76)
  - University Planning Group, UA002.002.076.00022 (Box 76)
  - University-Wide Conference, UA002.002.076.00023 (Box 76)
  - University-Wide Teaching Dec. 10, 2004, UA002.002.076.00024 (Box 76)
  - University-Wide Teaching Dec. 5, 2004, UA002.002.076.00025 (Box 76)
  - University-Wide Teaching, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.002.076.00026 (Box 76)
  - University-wide teaching, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.002.077.00001 (Box 77)
  - University-wide teaching, 1998; UA002.002.077.00002 (Box 77)
  - University-wide teaching, 1997; UA002.002.077.00003 (Box 77)
  - University-wide teaching, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.002.077.00004 (Box 77)
  - University-wide teaching, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.002.077.00005 (Box 77)
  - Walter Reed Army medical center, 1995; UA002.002.077.00006 (Box 77)
  - 80 web pages, 2002; UA002.002.077.00007 (Box 77)
  - Yale Medicine spring 2000, UA002.002.077.00008 (Box 77)
  - Zucker, UA002.002.077.00009 (Box 77)
  - 14th Annual Graduate Awards Presentation, 2012; UA002.002.079.00001 (Box 79)
  - Action Planning Committee for the President and Provost's Units, 2011; UA002.002.079.00002 (Box 79)
  - ALD AY, 2010 -- 2011; UA002.002.079.00003 (Box 79)
  - Boston Campus Mentoring Program Toolkit, 2007; UA002.002.079.00004 (Box 79)
  - Distance Education Planning Guide, 2005; UA002.002.079.00005 (Box 79)
  - Fidelity 1 Reports, 2007; UA002.002.079.00006 (Box 79)
  - Fidelity 2 Reports, 2008; UA002.002.079.00007 (Box 79)
  - Fidelity 3 Reports, 2010; UA002.002.079.00008 (Box 79)
  - Global Health Web Project, 2011; UA002.002.079.00009 (Box 79)
  - ITAC, 2011; UA002.002.079.00010 (Box 79)
  - Operating and Capital Budgets FY 2004-FY 2006, 2003; UA002.002.079.00011 (Box 79)
  - Project Proposal: A U.S.-India Partnership for Public Health, 2011; UA002.002.079.00012 (Box 79)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine Briefing to Tufts University Administration, Dean Phil Kosch, 2004; UA002.002.079.00013 (Box 79)
  - Blueprint for Tufts University, 2011; UA002.002.079.00014 (Box 79)
  - Student Safety Working Group, 2011 -- 2012; UA002.002.079.00015 (Box 79)
  - T10 Core Committee Final Reports, 2013; UA002.002.079.00016 (Box 79)
  - T10 Core Cross-Cutting Committees [1 of 4], 2012; UA002.002.079.00017 (Box 79)
  - T10 Core Cross-Cutting Committees [2 of 4], 2012; UA002.002.079.00018 (Box 79)
  - T10 Core Cross-Cutting Committees [3 of 4], 2012; UA002.002.079.00019 (Box 79)
  - T10 Core Cross-Cutting Committees [4 of 4], 2012; UA002.002.079.00020 (Box 79)
  - T10 Working Groups [1 of 5], 2012; UA002.002.079.00021 (Box 79)
  - T10 Working Groups [2 of 5], 2012; UA002.002.079.00022 (Box 79)
  - T10 Working Groups [3 of 5], 2012; UA002.002.079.00023 (Box 79)
  - T10 Working Groups [4 of 5], 2012; UA002.002.079.00024 (Box 79)
  - T10 Working Groups [5 of 5], 2012; UA002.002.079.00025 (Box 79)
  - TDLC, 2011; UA002.002.079.00026 (Box 79)
  - Tufts Computing and Communications Services FY 2004 Budget Proposal, 2002; UA002.002.079.00027 (Box 79)
  - University Information Technology Accomplishments, 2007; UA002.002.079.00028 (Box 79)
  - The Conversation, 2013-10-28; UA002.002285; 1 Web sites
    This website was created as part of the T10 strategic plan as a place to engage the Tufts community about the future of the University.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
- Department files, 1934 -- 1994; 1965 -- 1988; UA002.003; 3.9 Linear Feet
  This series contains the Provost's files on departments in Arts & Sciences and the university. Consists primarily of departmental reports to the provost, but also contains some correspondence. Each year every department must submit a report to the provost on their activities of the previous year. These reports may contain budget, program, and hiring information, as well as proposed curriculum, estimates on space allocations, and other program needs. Some reports are more formal than others. In some cases outside consultants were hired to conduct a study and write the report. The provost uses this information to make policy decisions. Often these reports are shared with the Academic Affairs Committee.
  There is significant overlap in types of records across previously processed material in "Department Files" (boxes 22-26), "Subject Files" (boxes 1-21) and "Correspondence" (boxes 27-30). As of July 2006, it was decided to not reprocess these old files but to prevent this kind of overlap in the future.
  - American Studies Program, proposal, 1980; UA002.003.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - American Studies Program, annual report, 1988; UA002.003.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Anatomy and Cellular Biology Dept, Chairman's narrative, 1985; UA002.003.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Anatomy and Cellular Biology Dept, appendices, 1985; UA002.003.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Anatomy and Cellular Biology Dept, letter, 1988; UA002.003.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, letters, 1965 -- 1975; UA002.003.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Arts and Sciences Dept, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.003.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Athletic Dept, 1964 -- 1982; UA002.003.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Athletic Dept, 1965 -- 1985; UA002.003.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - Biology, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1961 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Chemistry, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Chemistry, 1982 -- 1984; UA002.003.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - Chemistry Dept, Advisory Committee, 1985; UA002.003.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Child Study, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - Child Study Dept, 1976 -- 1986; UA002.003.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Civil Engineering, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Classics, 1969 -- 1977; UA002.003.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Classics Dept, annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - College of Engineering long-range planning, 1978; UA002.003.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - College of Engineering, 1984 -- 1987; UA002.003.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - College of Liberal Arts: Annual Reports, 1988; UA002.003.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Department of Engineering Design: Annual Report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.003.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Department of Engineering Design: Annual Report, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.003.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Department of Sociology & Antrhopology: Annual Report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.022.00025 (Box 22)